metalkingdom.net 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy | Metal Kingdom

Your privacy is important to Metal Kingdom and this policy represents our commitment to care for your personal information. 

This Privacy Policy sets out how we uses and protects any information that you give us when you use our website. 

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. 

**1\. Your Choices**

You can choose to enjoy content on our website without providing us directly with any information about you. However, some information may be collected or be requested so that you can take advantage of certain features and services offered on our website. 

**2\. Information Collected**

When you register on our website, we collect the following information. This Information is directly provided by you to our website.   
Required information : username, password and email address 

When you visit our website, we collect automatically certain information such as IP address, browser type and operating system. 

**3\. Use of Information**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service. We may use this information to improve our services. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. We have adopted commercially reasonable technical and physical procedures to help protect your information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access. 

**4\. Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amounts of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our services. 

**5\. Links to Other Websites**

Please note that our website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such linked sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. 

**6\. Third-Party Advertising**

Some of the advertising displayed on our website are delivered by third parties. The currently used third-party is Google. 

**7\. User-Generated Content**

Some our services enable users to submit their own content for use in boards and other functions. Publication of user-generated content on our website is subject to our Terms of Use. Please remember that any information you disclose becomes public information. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law or your personal privacy. 

**8\. Controlling Your Personal Information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: whenever you are asked to fill in a form on our website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want to collect the information. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

**9\. Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. We advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. These changes are effective immediately upon publishing. 

Last update: August 17, 2018
